AINUN NAWWARAH BINTI ZAHARRUDIN

GAME PROGRAMMER

Contact Info

(📞 +6014-3394200

red.hana0515@gmail.com

https://red-hana0515.github.io/

Soft Skills

Well-Organized Punctuality Eager to Learn

Language

Bahasa Malaysia

Native

English Spoken and Written

Japanese

Basic Reading

Interests

Creative Writing

Video Editing

Horror / Mystery Genres

Narrative-based

Reference

Johann Lim Tek Sen

Programme Leader of Computing and Creative Media UOWMKDU ts.lim@uow.edu.my

Yap Chin Kein

Lecturer of UOWMKDU ck.yap@uow.edu.my

(1) About Me

A senior college student majoring in game programming who has involved in multiple team projects. While I have few experience in certain game engines, I'm willing to learn and improve further knowledge on other game-related works, especially in the tech art department.

Education

June 2020 - May 2023

University of Wollongong Malaysia KDU

Bachelor of Game Development (Hons)

May 2019 - April 2020

University of Wollongong Malaysia KDU

Foundation Studies of Arts and Technology

Project Experiences

PASSAGE

- Sept 2022 May 2023 Final year project, made in Unity
 - · Tasked as 3D shader graphics programmer, VFX and UI technical artist
 - (Link to game later)

Jan 2022 - April 2022

PURRPATRATOR

- Mobile multiplayer game project, made in Unity
- Tasked as one of the mechanics programmer
- https://uowmgames.itch.io/purrpatrator

Sept 2021 - Dec 2021

- First game project, made in Unity
- 10,000 METERS DEEP Tasked as one of the mechanics programmer, video trailer editor
 - https://uowmgames.itch.io/10000-meters-deep

Skillset

UNITY **Advanced**

C++ Intermediate

PREMIER PRO Intermediate